Guide to the Wiltwyck School for Boys records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Wiltwyck School for Boys Records,
1942-1981
[Bulk Dates: 1964-1981]
Wiltwyck School for Boys.
20.58 linear feet (49 document boxes and one oversize archival box)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY. 10027
6262245
This collection contains the administrative records of the Wiltwyck School for Boys, a residential treatment center for troubled boys and adolescents from the New York City area.
Historical Note
The Wiltwyck School for Boys began as a project of the Episcopal City Mission Society in 1936, and was located in Esopus, New York. Initially, it was designed as an experimental summer camp for Protestant African-American juvenile delinquents and potential juvenile delinquents. The Children's Court required an institution that would accept these children, since state agencies and other private juvenile institutions did not address the needs of this population. After that initial summer, the institution decided to remain open year-round. Under the leadership of the Right Reverend William T. Manning, the first president of Wiltwyck, a gymnasium and a remodeled school building, which included room for professional and clerical staff, were built.
From the beginning, Wiltwyck emphasized the need for holistic treatment that included not only the boys, but also their families. In 1939, Esther Hilton, the director of a training unit for the New York School of Social Work, joined the staff, inaugurating Wiltwyck's extensive use of social workers and social work students in counseling the boys and their families.
In 1942, the Episcopal City Mission Society announced that it could no longer support Wiltwyck owing to the expense of its programs and the upkeep of the property. Recognizing the importance of this institution, a group of interested persons (including Judge Justine Polier Wise and Eleanor Roosevelt) assumed control of Wiltwyck, incorporating under the approval of the State Department of Social Welfare in 1942 as an interracial and non-sectarian institution. As part of its charter, Wiltwyck committed itself to a program of "moral and spiritual enlightenment, character development, correction of behavior problems, education and training for good citizenship" (Wiltwyck Charter, 1942).
In 1953, the school expanded its mission to include children and adolescents with severe emotional disturbances, serving yet another group that often fell through the cracks of the child welfare system. With the arrival of these children, Wiltwyck intensified its psychiatric counseling services, increasing the training requirements for its counselors and adding Dr. Edgar Auerswald as the Medical Director. The school also recognized the need for half-way houses in the boys' neighborhoods where they could re-adjust to life after their time at Wiltwyck, and purchased and remodeled two brownstones on East 18th Street which were called the Floyd Patterson Residence after one of Wiltwyck's most famous alumni, the boxer Floyd Patterson.
Given the growth of the population and the expansion of its mission, the Wiltwyck School required a larger, more up-to-date campus, and after several legal battles against zoning restrictions created by the town of Yorktown, New York in an attempt to bar Wiltwyck from buying land, the school moved to Yorktown to a campus named for Eleanor Roosevelt, who had been an active supporter of Wiltwyck from its inception. The new campus reflected Wiltwyck's treatment philosophy: open-plan buildings and unfenced grounds designed to give the boys a sense of freedom and responsibility for their environment.
In the 1970s, treatment models shifted away from residential institutions to a focus on smaller centers located in children's communities. In response to these changes in the larger therapeutic and psychiatric communities, Wiltwyck opened smaller centers in Bedford-Stuyvesant in Brooklyn, in the Bronx, and in lower Manhattan. Despite this expansion, the 1970s were a difficult time for Wiltwyck since New York City provided much of its funding. As the city underwent fiscal crisis, Wiltwyck experienced several budget crises of its own. Despite the Board of Directors' attempt to generate revenue through private donations, Wiltwyck went further and further into debt. At the same time, local community groups, outraged by Wiltwyck's policy that allowed students to wander the grounds freely, held a series of hearings designed to expose the inadequate nature of supervision and records oversight at the Eleanor Roosevelt Campus. In response to the severe funding crisis and community pressure, the school closed in 1981.
Eleanor Roosevelt, Anna Roosevelt, and Justine Polier Wise were among the supporters of Wiltwyck through its inception to its closing. Prominent alumni include Floyd Patterson and Claude Brown, the author of Manchild in the Promised Land, a memoir of his youth in Harlem, which he dedicated to Wiltwyck. Johnny Carson and Harry Belafonte were among Wiltwyck's most dedicated supporters, organizing and performing in benefits for Wiltwyck.
Scope and Content
The bulk of the collection is comprised of administrative records of the day-to-day functioning of the Wiltwyck School for Boys. These records include correspondence, meeting minutes, committee files, program descriptions and proposals, fundraising and public relations initiatives, publications by Wiltwyck staff, and oversize architectural drawings of the Wiltwyck campus. The collection contains a number of closed files dealing with individual patient care.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into five series and eight subseries:
Series I: Board of Directors Files, 1942-1980
Subseries I.1: Correspondence, 1967-1980
Subseries I.2: Subject Files, 1965-1980
Subseries I.3: Committee Files, 1968-1980
Subseries I.4: Meeting Minutes, 1942-1980
Series II: Executive Director Files, 1965-1981
Subseries II.1: Correspondence, 1970-1980
Subseries II.2: Subject Files, 1965-1981
Series III: Articles and Conference Papers, 1963-1978
Subseries III.1: Wiltwyck Stafff Articles and Conference Papers, 1963-1978
Subseries III.2: General Articles and Conference Papers, 1963-1978
Series IV: Printed Material, 1966-1975
Series V: Oversize Material, 1964-1981
Subjects
New York School of Social Work.; Belafonte, Harry, 1927-; Brown, Claude, 1937-; Carson, Johnny, 1925-2005.; Patterson, Floyd.; Polier, Justine Wise, 1903-1987.; Roosevelt, Anna, 1906-1975.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Group homes.; Juvenile delinquents--New York (State); Juvenile justice, Administration of--New York (State); Residential treatment for children & youth.; Social work with juvenile delinquents.; Status offenders.
Access Restrictions
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room. Please consult the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reference desk for further instructions.
There are several restricted files in the collection that deal with individual patient records. These files will be restricted for eighty years after the creation of the record. The earliest file will open in 2045 and the latest in 2061. The files are noted in the contents list.
Acquisition
Teachers College Library, Transfer July 2006 2005-2006-M57
Finding aid in repository; folder level control.
- Series I: Board of Directors Files, 1942-1981
  Series I holds the administrative files of the Board of Directors of the Wiltwyck School for Boys. This series is arranged in four subseries: Correspondence, Subject Files, Committee Files, and Meeting Minutes.
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence, 1967-1980
    This subseries contains the letters and memos of the Board of Directors. This correspondence is both corporate and individual; some letters and memos are written by the entire Board, while other letters and memos circulated between individuals both on and outside the Board.
    - Correspondence, 1967-1980, (3 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Union Free School District Board Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Subject Files, 1965-1980
    The Subject files hold financial records, bylaws, and member lists and files.
    - Audit, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Board Fund. 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bylaws, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1968 March (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Curriculum Vitae, Board of Directors, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Campus Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Financial Records, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Financial Statement, 1967 September 6 - 1969 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Fundraising, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Membership History, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Member Listing, 1966-1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Members' Orientation Program, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Members
      - Manheim, Anthony A, 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Oliensis, Sheldon, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Polier, Justine Wise, Honorary President, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Task Force on New York City Audit, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 3: Committee Files, 1968-1980
    This subseries is comprised of the records of the meetings and programs of the committees of the Board of Directors: Ad Hoc Committees, the Bronx Committee, the Brooklyn Committee, the Eleanor Roosevelt Campus Committee, the Fundraising Committee, the Manhattan Committee, the Program and Treatment Committee, and the Yorktown Union Free School District Committee, among others.
    - Ad Hoc Committee
      - Board/Staff Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - New Structure and Future Program, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Search Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Wiltwyck Program Review Task Force, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Wiltwyck Program Review Task Force, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Wiltwyck Program Review Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Bronx Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Brooklyn Committee, 1974-5 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Building and Development Fund Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Building and Development Fund Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Committee Lists 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Committee on Committees 1968 June (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Campus and House Committee 1968 January-1978 January (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Campus Committee 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Executive Committee 1968 January-1970 January, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Fundraising Foundation Subcommittee, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Geographic Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Law Committee, 1967 November -1968 May (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Manhattan Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Merger Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - New York City Division Committee, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Program and Treatment Committee, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Public Relations Committee--Journal Subcommittee, 1974-5 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Residential Operations Committee 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Search Committee, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Search Committee for Executive Director, 1978-9 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Social Action Committee, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Special Committee to Implement Board Decisions, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Yorktown Union Free School District 1973 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Subseries 4: Meeting Minutes, 1942-1981
    The Meeting Minutes record the meetings of the Board of Directors. They also include reports from committees and subcommittees, supporting documentation of financial and legal issues, and comments from members of the Board.
    - 1942 June 11-1951 June 4, (6 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 51-56)
    - 1951 December 13-1962 December 13, (12 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 57-68)
    - 1963 January 24-1971 June 24, (11 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 69-79)
    - 1971 September 23-1976 December 9, (8 Folders) (Box 6, Folder 80-87)
    - 1977 September 15-1981 April 23, (5 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 88-93)
- Series II: Executive Director Files, 1942-1981
  This series consists of the Executive Director’s administrative files, including correspondence, program initiatives, material pertaining to Wiltwyck’s connections with state and city agencies, and the day-to-day functioning of Wiltwyck, including the Eleanor Roosevelt Campus, Floyd Patterson House, and the Group Homes in Brooklyn, Manhattan, and the Bronx. This series is arranged in two subseries: Correspondence and Subject Files.
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence Files, 1970-1980
    The Correspondence files contain the letters and memos of the Executive Director, T. George Silcott. His letters and memos are directed to Wiltwyck staff and members of Board of Directors as well as individuals and organizations outside of Wiltwyck.
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1970-1972, (6 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 94-99)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1973-1979, (13 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 100-112)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973, (2 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 113-114)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1981, (5 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 115-119)
    - Correspondence, Union Free School Board, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Subseries 2: Subject Files, 1965-1981
    The Subject files contain the administrative files of the Wiltwyck School for Boys, including Group Home files, Eleanor Roosevelt Campus files, Floyd Patterson House files, and Yorktown Union Free School District files. These files also hold documents dealing with New York City and State agencies, programs and projects developed by Wiltwyck staff, fundraising and public relations material, and other files dealing with the daily functioning of the organization.
    - Activities, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Ad Hoc Committee--The Rights of Children in Care, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Administration, 1973-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 123-125)
    - Admissions and Discharges, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Adolescent Unit
      - 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 127)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 128)
        [restricted until 2055]
    - Affiliations (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Aftercare, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 129)
      [restricted until 2053]
    - Agency Manual, 1972-1974, (3 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 130-132)
    - Agency-Operated Boarding Houses, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1966 (Box 9)
    - American Association of Psychiatric Services for Children, 1974-1976, (3 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 134-136)
    - American Orthopsychiatric Association, 1973-1977, (4 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 137-140)
    - Annual Report, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Application for Outpatient Facility Operating License, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - Association of Administrators in Mental Health and Mental Retardation Facilities, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Association of Black Administrators in Social Welfare, 1973-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 144-145)
    - Association of Black Social Workers, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Audit, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Banks, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Bar Association--City of New York, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Barker, Pat--Eleanor Roosevelt Campus, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Better Business Bureau, 1975-1979, (2 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 151-152)
    - Better Chance, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 153)
    - Black Administrators in Child Welfare, 1973-1976, (3 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 154-156)
    - Black Agency Executives, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 157)
    - Black Child Development Institute, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Black and Puerto Rican Legislative Caucus, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Bloom, Daniel, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 160)
      (one Fish Relief chart in oversize Box)
    - Board of Cooperative Educational Services, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Board Day Carnival, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Board of Directors, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Board-Staff Administration Committee Minutes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Boys' Assignments, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 165)
      [restricted until 2052]
    - Boys' Handbook, undated (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Boy's Vacation, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Bronfman Foundation, Inc., 1980 (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - Bronx
      - Center, 1971-1980, (7 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 169-175)
      - Storefront, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 176)
      - Unit, 1973-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 177-179)
    - Brooklyn
      - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 180)
      - Bedford-Stuyvesant Center, 1975-1979, (4 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 181-184)
      - Bedford-Stuyvesant Center--Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 185)
      - Bedford-Stuyvesant Center--Reports, 1975-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 186-187)
      - Brooklyn Center, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 188)
      - Brownsville, 1975-1977, (3 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 189-191)
      - Brownsville--Reports, 1975-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 192-193)
      - Central Brooklyn Committee on Youth and Family Services, 1974-75 (Box 12, Folder 194)
      - Diagnostic Adolescent Service Center Project, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 195)
      - Diversion Committee, 1975-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 196-197)
      - Project, 1972-1975, (4 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 198-201)
      - Real Estate, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 202)
      - Reports, 1974-5 (Box 12, Folder 203)
      - St. Benedict's and St. Mathew's, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 204)
      - Summary and Project, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 205)
      - Unit, 1973-1974, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 206-207)
    - Bureau of Child Welfare, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 208-210)
    - Bydale Foundation, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 211)
    - Calendar
      - 1972 (Box 13, Folder 212)
      - Winter 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 213)
    - Campus Operations, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 214)
    - Campus Regulations, 1973-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 215-217)
    - Career Center for Social Services, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 218)
    - Census Information, 1971-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 219-220)
    - Census Information, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 221)
      [restricted until 2054]
    - Central Brooklyn Coordinating Council, 1977-79, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 222-223)
    - Child Abuse and Neglect Conferences, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 224)
    - Child Advocacy Project, undated (Box 13, Folder 225)
    - Child Study Association, 1971-1978 (Box 13, Folder 226)
    - Child Welfare Information Services, 1975-1978, (3 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 227-229)
    - Child Welfare League of America, 1974-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 230-231)
    - Christmas Program, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 233)
      [restricted until 2058]
    - Citizens' Committee for Children, 1974-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 234-236)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children, 1974-1976, (8 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 237-244)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children, 1976-1980, (6 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 245-250)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children--Group Home Task Force, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 251)
    - Class Action Lawsuit, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - Coalition of Voluntary Mental Health and Mental Retardation Services, 1973-1979, (4 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 253-256)
    - College of Human Services 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 257)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work, 1971-1980, (3 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 258-260)
    - Committees
      - Drug Abuse, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 261)
      - Safety, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 262)
      - Volunteer, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 263)
    - Community-Based Alternative School Program, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 264)
    - Community Care Program, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 265)
    - Community Contacts, 1973-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 266-268)
    - Community Council of Greater New York, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 269)
    - Community Council of Greater New York, 1976-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 270-271)
    - Community Mental Health Services, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 272)
    - Community Organization File, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 273)
    - Community Services, 1977-1981, (4 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 274-280)
    - Comunity Services Administration, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
    - Community Service Society of New York, 1974-1978, (3 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 281-283)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1973-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 284-285)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1973-1978, (3 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 286-288)
    - Concerned Black Citizens, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 289)
    - Concerned Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 290)
    - Conferences, 1973-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 291-292)
    - Conference Abstracts, undated (Box 16, Folder 293)
    - Consulting Psychiatrists, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 294)
    - Cornell University, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 295)
    - Corporal Punishment, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 296)
    - Corporation Bylaws, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 297)
    - Corporation Certificate of Incorporation and Not-for-Profit Status, 1973, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 298-299)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1970-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 300-301)
    - Criminal Justice Coordinating Council, 1973-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 302-303)
    - Curriculum Sub-Committee, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 304)
    - Daily Logs, 1980 September (Box 17, Folder 305)
      [restricted until 2060]
    - Damage, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 306)
    - Dell'Angelo, June 1978 (Box 17, Folder 307)
    - Director for Inter-Agency Relations, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 308)
    - Directories, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 309)
    - Discharges, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 310)
    - Dream Lake Campus--Plans and Interior Furnishing, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 311)
      (one architectural drawing in oversize Box)
    - Drugs, undated (Box 17, Folder 312)
    - Duke University, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 313)
    - Dutchess County, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 314)
    - Early Childhood Development, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 315)
    - Einstein College of Medicine, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 316)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Campus, 1970-1981, (7 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 317-323)
      (1978 file is)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Campus
      - Accidents Reports, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 324)
        [restricted until 2049]
      - Activities--Boy Scout Troup, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 325)
      - Activities Schedule, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 326)
      - Admissions Policy, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 327)
      - Boys' Daily Routine Schedule (Box 17, Folder 328)
      - Boy Scout Institutional Workshop, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 339)
      - Cabinet, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 340)
      - Case Conference Material, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 341)
        [restricted until 2047]
      - Child Care, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 342)
      - Child Care Staff, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 343)
      - Child Care Supervisors, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 344)
      - Children's Services, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 345-346)
      - Clinical Department, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 347)
      - Counselor Orientation Folder, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 348)
      - Counselor-Teacher Meetings, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 349)
      - Creative Arts Program, undated (Box 18, Folder 350)
      - Cross Country Team Proposal, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 351)
      - Discharges, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 352)
      - Executive Cabinet, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 353)
      - Fiscal Departmen--Audit Report, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 354)
      - Group-Therapist Meetings, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 355)
      - Holder, Melvin, undated (Box 18, Folder 356)
      - In-Service Training Program 1967 September (Box 18, Folder 357)
      - Inter-departmental Staff Meetings, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 358)
      - Lance, Bart, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 359)
      - Modified Residential Program, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 360)